<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name_upgrade_postfix">Pro</string>

    <string name="upgrades_dashcard_title">Upgrade SD Maid SE</string>
    <string name="upgrades_dashcard_body">SD Maid SE Pro offers better results, more features and options for power users.</string>
    <string name="upgrades_dashcard_upgrade_action">Upgrade</string>

    <string name="upgrades_gplay_unavailable_error_title">Google Play is unavailable</string>
    <string name="upgrades_gplay_unavailable_error_description">SD Maid can\'t connect to Google Play. Is Google Play installed and up to date? Is your Google Account logged in? Try clearing the cache of the Google Play app and rebooting your device.</string>
    <string name="upgrades_gplay_billing_error_label">Google Play Issue</string>
    <string name="upgrades_gplay_billing_error_description">There was a problem with Google Play. Please try again later or restart your device.\n\nDetails: %s</string>

    <string name="upgrades_gplay_internal_error_title">Google Play error</string>
    <string name="upgrades_gplay_internal_error_description">An internal Google Play error occurred. Please try the following:\n\n• Restart your device\n• Clear Google Play Store cache\n• Try again later</string>

    <string name="upgrades_gplay_network_error_title">Connection error</string>
    <string name="upgrades_gplay_network_error_description">Unable to connect to Google Play. Please check your internet connection and try again.</string>

    <string name="upgrades_gplay_already_owned_error_title">Already purchased</string>
    <string name="upgrades_gplay_already_owned_error_description">Use the \"Restore purchase\" option to restore your purchase. If the issue persists, try clearing Google Play cache and restarting your device.</string>

    <string name="upgrade_screen_title">Get SD Maid SE Pro</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_preamble">SD Maid has no ads and doesn\'t sell user data. My work is financed by you ❤️.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_benefits_title">Upgrade benefits</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_benefits_body">• Clean app caches and expendable data\n• Remove duplicate files\n• Enable scheduled cleanups\n• Create custom filters and cleanup rules\n• Track storage trends and cleanup history\n• More features and controls across the app\n• Support continued development</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_offers_title">Upgrade options</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_offers_body">Same features, just different pricing models.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_offers_or">or</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_subscription_offer_title">Yearly subscription</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_subscription_offer_body">Renews yearly after the free trial. Cancel anytime in Google Play.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_subscription_offer_body_no_trial">Renews yearly. Cancel anytime in Google Play.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_iap_offer_title">Buy once</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_iap_offer_body">One payment, no renewals.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_offers_unavailable_message">Prices couldn\'t be loaded right now. Check Google Play and try again in a moment.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_subscription_trial_action">Start free 14-day trial</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_subscription_action">Subscribe</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_iap_action">One-time purchase</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_thanks_toast">You are the best! ❤️</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_restore_purchase_action">Restore purchase</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_restore_banner_title">Already bought Pro?</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_restore_banner_body">It looks like you upgraded to Pro on this device before. Restore your purchase to unlock it again.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_restore_sync_patience_hint">Play Store synchronization may take time. Try rebooting, clearing Google Play cache or simply wait.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_restore_multiaccount_hint">Multiple accounts can confuse Google Play. Install the app through the Google Play website, which forces associations with a specific account.</string>

    <string name="upgrade_screen_owned_hero_title">Congratulations!</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_owned_hero_sub_body">You have %1$s, unlocked by your subscription.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_owned_hero_iap_body">You have %1$s, unlocked by your one-time purchase.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_owned_iap_title">One-time purchase</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_owned_iap_body">You own the one-time Pro upgrade. Pro stays unlocked on this Google account. Thanks for supporting SD Maid ❤️.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_owned_sub_renewing_body">Your Pro subscription is active and set to renew. Billing is managed by Google Play.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_owned_iap_locked_note">Prefer the one-time purchase? It becomes available once your subscription is no longer set to renew. Cancel the subscription in Google Play to switch.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_owned_sub_not_renewing_body">Your Pro subscription is active, but not set to renew. Pro stays available until the current period ends.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_owned_both_renewing_warning">This subscription is still set to renew, although you already own the one-time upgrade. You can cancel it in Google Play.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_manage_subscription_action">Manage subscription</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_owned_iap_purchase_note">This is a separate purchase: it does not cancel or refund your subscription. Use the same Google account for both.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_sub_still_renewing_title">Subscription still active</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_sub_still_renewing_message">Google Play reports that your subscription is still set to renew. To buy the one-time upgrade, cancel the subscription in Google Play first, then come back here.\n\nJust cancelled it? Give Google Play a moment and try again. Also make sure you are using the same Google account.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_sub_check_failed_message">Couldn\'t check your subscription status with Google Play. Please try again in a moment.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_restore_success_message">Purchase restored, your Pro upgrade is active.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_grace_title">Confirming your purchase</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_grace_body_short">Pro is still active. Waiting for Google Play to re-confirm your purchase, all Pro features stay unlocked in the meantime.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_grace_body">Pro is still active, but Google Play hasn\'t confirmed your purchase for a while. If you bought Pro, restore the purchase and check that Google Play uses the account that bought it. If the subscription ended or the purchase was refunded, Pro will turn off by itself, nothing else to do.</string>

    <string name="upgrade_screen_restore_body">Restoring asks Google Play to re-check this app\'s purchases for the current account. It does not start a new purchase.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_restore_status_title">Status looks wrong?</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_restore_status_body">If a purchase is missing or this status looks incorrect, re-check with Google Play.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_contact_support_action">Contact support</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_restore_checked_message">SD Maid just checked Google Play, but no Pro purchase could be confirmed for the account Google Play is using for this app.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_screen_restore_contact_hint">Still stuck? Contact support from the email that made the purchase and include your Google Play order number.</string>
</resources>
